Guide to the John Penley Photographs and Papers TAM 501
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Photographs, circa 1980-2013
  - Medical Marijuana buyers club benefit Johann Moore, Penny Arcade, Mac Mcgill, circa 1990-2000 (Box 14, Folder 062-N)
  - Medical Marijuana buyers club benefit Johann Moore, Penny Arcade, Mac Mcgill, circa 1990-2000 (Box 7, Folder 062-P)
  - Musicians, circa 1990-2000 (Box 14, Folder 063-N)
  - Musicians, circa 1990-2000 (Box 7, Folder 063-P)
  - Charas event, Roland Bolan, circa 1990-2000 (Box 14, Folder 064-N)
  - Charas event, Roland Bolan, circa 1990-2000 (Box 7, Folder 064-P)
  - Lower Manhattan together event Marguarita Lopez others, circa 1990-2000 (Box 14, Folder 065-N)
  - Lower Manhattan together event Marguarita Lopez others, circa 1990-2000 (Box 7, Folder 065-P)
  - Opening of Housing Works aids housing building on Ave D with Director Charles King others, circa 1990-2000 (Box 14, Folder 066-N)
  - Opening of Housing Works aids housing building on Ave D with Director Charles King others, circa 1990-2000 (Box 7, Folder 066-P)
  - La Plaza cultural reopening ceremony with Margurita Lopez, other politicians squatters and others, circa 1990-2000 (Box 14, Folder 067-N)
  - La Plaza cultural reopening ceremony with Margurita Lopez, other politicians squatters and others, circa 1990-2000 (Box 7, Folder 067-P)
  - Democratic National Convention protest Chicago, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 068-N)
  - Democratic National Convention protest Chicago, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 068-P)
  - NY Post drivers strike protest Norman Siegel, circa 1990-2000 (Box 14, Folder 069-N)
  - NY Post drivers strike protest Norman Siegel, circa 1990-2000 (Box 7, Folder 069-P)
  - Wigstock Chelsea Pier great colorful pix, circa 1990-2000 (Box 14, Folder 070-N)
  - Wigstock Chelsea Pier great colorful pix, circa 1990-2000 (Box 7, Folder 070-P)
  - ACT UP and Housing Works protest on Brooklyn Bridge arrests and great anti Guiliani signs lots of good stuff, circa 1990-2000 (Box 14, Folder 071-N)
  - ACT UP and Housing Works protest on Brooklyn Bridge arrests and great anti Guiliani signs lots of good stuff, circa 1990-2000 (Box 7, Folder 071-P)
  - Anti Drug War protest Chicago Democratic National Convention, circa 1990-2000 (Box 14, Folder 072-N)
  - Anti Drug War protest Chicago Democratic National Convention, circa 1990-2000 (Box 7, Folder 072-P)
  - Parks Commissioner Henry Stern opening of new dog run at Tompkins Square Park, circa 1990-2000 (Box 14, Folder 073-N)
  - Parks Commissioner Henry Stern opening of new dog run at Tompkins Square Park, circa 1990-2000 (Box 7, Folder 073-P)
  - Lynne Stewart, Stanley Cohen, Ralph Poynter state supreme court, circa 1990-2000 (Box 14, Folder 074-N)
  - Lynne Stewart, Stanley Cohen, Ralph Poynter state supreme court, circa 1990-2000 (Box 7, Folder 074-P)
  - Cooper Union Politicians event, circa 1990-2000 (Box 14, Folder 075-N)
  - Cooper Union Politicians event, circa 1990-2000 (Box 7, Folder 075-P)
  - Little soldiers LES boys group, E13 St. squatter community center party lots of squatters, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 076-N)
  - Little soldiers LES boys group, E13 St. squatter community center party lots of squatters, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 076-P)
  - Guiliani is a dope marijuana is medicine pot protest, great signs, arrests, Dennis Peron, circa 1990-2000 (Box 14, Folder 077-N)
  - Guiliani is a dope marijuana is medicine pot protest, great signs, arrests, Dennis Peron, circa 1990-2000 (Box 7, Folder 077-P)
  - Armando Perez funeral very Puerto Rican traditions etc etc Margurita Lopes, Carmen Pabon LES mother Theresa, circa 1990-2000 (Box 14, Folder 078-N)
  - Armando Perez funeral very Puerto Rican traditions etc etc Margurita Lopes, Carmen Pabon LES mother Theresa, circa 1990-2000 (Box 7, Folder 078-P)
  - Emergency Services LES accident, circa 1990-2000 (Box 14, Folder 080-N)
  - Emergency Services LES accident, circa 1990-2000 (Box 7, Folder 080-P)
  - Acapulco Mexico, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 081-N)
  - Acapulco Mexico, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 081-P)
  - Stanley Cohen Paul Direnzo with cops, circa 1990-2000 (Box 14, Folder 082-N)
  - Stanley Cohen Paul Direnzo with cops, circa 1990-2000 (Box 7, Folder 082-P)
  - Crime Scene police shoot and kill kid on Ave D, circa 1990-2000 (Box 14, Folder 083-N)
  - Crime Scene police shoot and kill kid on Ave D, circa 1990-2000 (Box 7, Folder 083-P)
  - Zipolite, Oaxaco Mex. Coco Loco, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 084-N)
  - Zipolite, Oaxaco Mex. Coco Loco, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 084-P)
  - Fisherman's kids Estachuites Mexico, circa 1990-2000 (Box 7, Folder 084-P)
  - Anti Death Penalty rally Times Square Norman Siegel, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 085-N)
  - Anti Death Penalty rally Times Square Norman Siegel, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 085-P)
  - Hotel 17 party, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 086-N)
  - Hotel 17 party, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 086-P)
  - Bread and Puppett Democratic National Convention Dave Dellinger, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 087-N)
  - Bread and Puppett Democratic National Convention Dave Dellinger, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 087-P)
  - Hotel 17 wild sex party, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 088-N)
  - Hotel 17 wild sex party, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 088-P)
  - Political funeral Act Up, circa 1990-2000 (Box 7, Folder 089-P)
  - Wigstock, Lady Bunny, Rudy Sucks written on someones ass, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 090-N)
  - Wigstock, Lady Bunny, Rudy Sucks written on someones ass, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 090-P)
  - Medical marijuana Dennis Peron, Dana Beal, circa 1990-2000 (Box 7, Folder 091-P)
  - Bob Marion in Tompkins Square Park, circa 1990-2000 (Box 7, Folder 091-P)
  - Crime Scene shooting of Second Ave deli owner, circa 1990-2000 (Box 14, Folder 092-N)
  - Crime Scene shooting of Second Ave deli owner, circa 1990-2000 (Box 7, Folder 092-P)
  - NYC tattoo convention awards, circa 1990-2000 (Box 14, Folder 093-N)
  - NYC tattoo convention awards, circa 1990-2000 (Box 7, Folder 093-P)
  - Purim celebration squatted synagogue LES, circa 1990-2000 (Box 14, Folder 094-N)
  - Purim celebration squatted synagogue LES, circa 1990-2000 (Box 7, Folder 094-P)
  - Crime scene Second Ave deli owner shooting, circa 1990-2000 (Box 14, Folder 095-N)
  - Crime scene Second Ave deli owner shooting, circa 1990-2000 (Box 7, Folder 095-P)
  - Margurita Lopez campaign rally in the projects. Photo of Lynne Stewart and Stanley Cohen, circa 1990-2000 (Box 14, Folder 096-N)
  - Margurita Lopez campaign rally in the projects. Photo of Lynne Stewart and Stanley Cohen, circa 1990-2000 (Box 7, Folder 096-P)
  - Me and Peter Levasseur on Fire Island the Pines, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 097-N)
  - Me and Peter Levasseur on Fire Island the Pines, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 097-P)
  - Housing march and event in Tompkins Square Park, LOISAIDA banner by Seth Tobocman, Margurita Lopez, Fran Luck speaking at TSP, circa 1990-2000 (Box 14, Folder 098-N)
  - Housing march and event in Tompkins Square Park, LOISAIDA banner by Seth Tobocman, Margurita Lopez, Fran Luck speaking at TSP, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 098-P)
  - Sister Mary Kelleher longtime housing advocate at candlelight vigil, circa 1990-2000 (Box 14, Folder 099-N)
  - Sister Mary Kelleher longtime housing advocate at candlelight vigil, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 099-P)
  - Roger Manning with guitar, circa 1990-2000 (Box 14, Folder 100-N)
  - Roger Manning with guitar, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 100-P)
  - Crazy party, homeless men on the street, circa 1990-2000 (Box 14, Folder 101-N)
  - Crazy party, homeless men on the street, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 101-P)
  - Rudy Guiliani at opening of family drug counseling center with cop who was shot there by drug dealers, circa 1990-2000 (Box 14, Folder 102-N)
  - Rudy Guiliani at opening of family drug counseling center with cop who was shot there by drug dealers, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 102-P)
  - Judith Malina, Xavier Wardlaw 13 St squat community center, Armando Perez with Rolando Politti, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 103-P)
  - Tompkins Square Park Library, circa 1990-2000 (Box 14, Folder 104-N)
  - Tompkins Square Park Library, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 104-P)
  - Wigstock, circa 1990-2000 (Box 14, Folder 105-N)
  - Wigstock, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 105-P)
  - Tattoo convention and protest in support of undocumented immigrants, circa 1990-2000 (Box 15, Folder 106-N)
  - Tattoo convention and protest in support of undocumented immigrants, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 106-P)
  - William Kunstler Memorial family members his daughters Ron Kuby others, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 107-P)
  - Margurita Lopez swearing in ceremony, circa 1990-2000 (Box 15, Folder 108-N)
  - Margurita Lopez swearing in ceremony, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 108-P)
  - B52 bar, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 109-P)
  - Squatter concert at the gas station Eric Drooker, Stephan Said aka Stephan Smith, circa 1990-2000 (Box 15, Folder 110-N)
  - Squatter concert at the gas station Eric Drooker, Stephan Said aka Stephan Smith, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 110-P)
  - Father George Kuhn speaks at Act Up rally, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 113-P)
  - Adult Education class Tompkins Square Library, circa 1990-2000 (Box 15, Folder 114-N)
  - Adult Education class Tompkins Square Library, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 114-P)
  - Housing Works and Act Up march against Councilman Antonio Pagan, circa 1990-2000 (Box 15, Folder 115-N)
  - Housing Works and Act Up march against Councilman Antonio Pagan, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 115-P)
  - NYC tattoo convention with shots of Coney Island historical freak show banners, circa 1990-2000 (Box 15, Folder 116-N)
  - NYC tattoo convention with shots of Coney Island historical freak show banners, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 116-P)
  - Village Voice news box with don't catch aids sticker on it, Medical Marijuana rally City Hall Dana Beal, circa 1990-2000 (Box 15, Folder 117-N)
  - Village Voice news box with don't catch aids sticker on it, Medical Marijuana rally City Hall Dana Beal, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 117-P)
  - Rent Control protest against Gov Pataki at South St Seaport, circa 1990-2000 (Box 15, Folder 118-N)
  - Rent Control protest against Gov Pataki at South St Seaport, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 118-P)
  - Pot smoke in Dana Beal Dennis Peron and Jerry the peddler squat pig roast, circa 1990-2000 (Box 15, Folder 119-N)
  - Pot smoke in Dana Beal Dennis Peron and Jerry the peddler squat pig roast, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 119-P)
  - Democratic National Convention protest Tom Hayden in Chicago, circa 1990-2000 (Box 15, Folder 120-N)
  - Democratic National Convention protest Tom Hayden in Chicago, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 120-P)
  - Mexico Puerto Angel, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 133-P)
  - Anti fur protest Bob Barker, circa 1990-2000 (Box 15, Folder 134-N)
  - Anti fur protest Bob Barker, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 134-P)
  - Reclaim the Streets anti Guiliani protest, circa 1990-2000 (Box 15, Folder 135-N)
  - Reclaim the Streets anti Guiliani protest, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 135-P)
  - Blackout Bookstore closing Brad Will takes sign down, circa 1990-2000 (Box 15, Folder 136-N)
  - Blackout Bookstore closing Brad Will takes sign down, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 136-P)
  - Guardian Angels Curtis Sliwa with Lisa Sliwa now Lisa Evers Fox local news reporter also Councilman Antonio Pagan with Curtis Sliwa, circa 1990-2000 (Box 15, Folder 143-N)
  - Guardian Angels Curtis Sliwa with Lisa Sliwa now Lisa Evers Fox local news reporter also Councilman Antonio Pagan with Curtis Sliwa, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 143-P)
  - Father George Kuhn with Tibetan monks Tspark, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 145-P)
  - Nicaragua, circa 1980-1990 (Box 8, Folder 146-P)
  - Dean Johnson and Dean and the weenies band dean is bald man in dress, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 147-P)
  - Leon, Nigaragua, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 149-P)
  - Central Park, circa 1990-2000 (Box 15, Folder 150-N)
  - Central Park, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 150-P)
  - Nicaragua, Savannah River plant sign, Philip Berrigan, circa 1980-1990 (Box 8, Folder 151-P)
  - Liberate Washington Square park protest, Anti El Salvador death squad protest NYC, circa 1990-2000 (Box 15, Folder 152-N)
  - Liberate Washington Square park protest, Anti El Salvador death squad protest NYC, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 152-P)
  - Taylor Meade with x wife Nozomi and her band at Cave Canem, circa 1990-2000 (Box 15, Folder 158-N)
  - Taylor Meade with x wife Nozomi and her band at Cave Canem, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 158-P)
  - Sonny Barger riding motorcycle Hells Angels, circa 1990-2000 (Box 15, Folder 159-N)
  - Sonny Barger riding motorcycle Hells Angels, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 159-P)
  - St Marks poetry annual New Years reading Penny Arcade, Margo Howard Howard in drag the ugliest drag queen in history, circa 1980-1990 (Box 8, Folder 160-P)
  - Nicaragua, circa 1980-1990 (Box 8, Folder 162-P)
  - Penny Arcade at medical marijuana benefit, circa 1990-2000 (Box 15, Folder 163-N)
  - Penny Arcade at medical marijuana benefit, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 163-P)
  - High Times mag party with Keith Stroup NORML, circa 1990-2000 (Box 15, Folder 164-N)
  - High Times mag party with Keith Stroup NORML, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 164-P)
  - Martin Sheen and Daniel Berrigan homeless protest, Koch as devil banner, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 165-P)
  - Mohawk Indian protest, AIDS housing protest, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 166-P)
  - Good photos. Protest after police shooting of teen on Ave D Al Sharpton, Sister Elisabeth Kelleher, Margurita Lopez, circa 1990-2000 (Box 15, Folder 168-N)
  - Good photos. Protest after police shooting of teen on Ave D Al Sharpton, Sister Elisabeth Kelleher, Margurita Lopez, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 168-P)
  - Anti and pro Bush protesters good signs, circa 1990-2000 (Box 15, Folder 169-N)
  - Anti and pro Bush protesters good signs, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 169-P)
  - Catholic reenactment of crucifixion of Christ Tompkins Square on Easter, circa 1990-2000 (Box 15, Folder 170-N)
  - Catholic reenactment of crucifixion of Christ Tompkins Square on Easter, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 170-P)
  - Random shots Lower East Side, circa 1980-1990 (Box 8, Folder 172-P)
  - Feeding the homeless, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 173-P)
  - Attorney Stanley Cohen with supporters of Hamas, circa 1990-2000 (Box 15, Folder 174-N)
  - Attorney Stanley Cohen with supporters of Hamas, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 174-P)
  - ABC NO RIO punk rock show, Fly's mural on front of ABC good stuff, circa 1990-2000 (Box 15, Folder 175-N)
  - ABC NO RIO punk rock show, Fly's mural on front of ABC good stuff, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 175-P)
  - Abbie Hoffman memorial with Margaret Kunstler, Johanna Lawrenson others, circa 1990-2000 (Box 15, Folder 176-N)
  - Abbie Hoffman memorial with Margaret Kunstler, Johanna Lawrenson others, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 176-P)
  - Hare Krishna punk rock benefit, circa 1990-2000 (Box 15, Folder 177-N)
  - Hare Krishna punk rock benefit, circa 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 177-P)
  - CBGB punk rock show, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 257-P)
  - Jonathan Shaw legendary tattoo artist, Legs McNeil reading from his book Please Kill Me, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 258-P)
  - Zapatistas San Christobal De Las Casas Mexico, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 259-P)
  - Stop the drug war rally William Kunstler Statue of Liberty t shirt, with Dana Beal, Dhrouba Bin Wahad Black Panther and Living Theater anti death penalty play with Judith Malina, Hannon Resnikof, Garrick Beck other living theater cast, undated (Box 10, Folder 260-P)
  - Housing Works housing facility ground breaking ceremony, circa 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 261-P)
  - Central Park pot and hemp rally Dhrouba Bin Wahad, circa 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 262-P)
  - Roller skate basketball tournament, x girlfriend Victoria Larsen, circa 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 263-P)
  - Acapulco Mexico, circa 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 264-P)
  - Al Sharpton and others at march against budget cuts, circa 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 266-P)
  - Stop the war on the poor rally, medical marijuana rally, circa 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 267-P)
  - Gay Pride, Radical Fairies, Judy Garland commemoration, ACT UP good stuff, circa 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 268-P)
  - Pot rally Washington Square Park, circa 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 269-P)
  - Tom Duane, Gay Pride, people get naked as a protest at St Patricks Cathedral, circa 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 270-P)
  - Sofie's bar LES, circa 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 271-P)
  - Joe Papp landmark dedication ceremony, circa 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 272-P)
  - Dykes Night Out protest against violence against lesbians, circa 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 273-P)
  - Protest at Rudy Guiliani speaking engagement, homeless death clock good photos, circa 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 274-P)
  - School Program LES, circa 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 275-P)
  - Henry Stern at park, Perry Masco white woman, Kid Lucky with mad cow t shirt, circa 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 280-P)
  - Rally to save Charas community center great stuff, circa 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 281-P)
  - Pot march Aron Kay, 7th annual squatters mayday, Iternity black woman speaking, circa 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 282-P)
  - Fire scene LES, metal jam Tompkins Square, Save community gardens meeting Paula Hewlett, circa 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 283-P)
  - Woman with Mumia T shirt, Ave C annual street fair Latino party, circa 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 284-P)
  - Palenque Mexico ruins observatory, circa 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 285-P)
  - Democratic convention Chicago Andrew Hoffman, circa 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 286-P)
  - Democratic convention Chicago one of the original Chicago 8 defendants with Dennis Peron, circa 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 287-P)
  - Zipolite Oaxaca Mexico, circa 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 288-P)
  - David Dellinger one of original Chicago 8 defendants, circa 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 290-P)
  - Democratic Convention NY Billioniares for Bush, Revolutionary Communist Party, circa 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 291-P)
  - Funeral for kid shot by police, Key Food Ave A, circa 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 292-P)
  - Last Free Festival at Woodstock Yasgurs farm near Bethel NY, Arlo Guthrie, Richie Havens lots of others, circa 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 293-P)
  - Democratic Convention Protest Chicago Ibogaine protest Rennie Davis, circa 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 294-P)
  - Squatter concert Tompkins Square Park, Allen Ginsberg, John the Communist, David Peel, Clayton Patterson, Chris Flash Shadow newspaper, circa 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 295-P)
  - St Marks Hotel, circa 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 296-P)
  - Billionaires For Bush, John Penley in Zipolite Oaxaca Mexico, circa 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 297-P)
  - Veterans for peace, Revolutionary Communist party, Mumia Jamal supporters others at Unity March Philly interesting signs visuals, circa 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 298-P)
  - Democratic convention NYC, Anti Clinton puppet, anti war stuff, Steve Cannon in Tribes Gallery E 3rd and C, circa 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 299-P)
  - Republican national convention protests Philadelphia F George Bush, circa 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 300-P)
  - Joan Rivers, Dana Beal, Mark Kramer, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 301-P)
  - Seth Tobocman and parents, Barbara Robin Lee engagement party Gramercy Park Synagogue, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 302-P)
  - Democratic Convention Chicago Ben Masel with cops, Rob McDonald with missile, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 303-P)
  - Armando Perez funeral Charas Susan Sarandon, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 304-P)
  - Protesters using police barricade as see saw Ave A, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 304-P)
  - Democratic Convention NYC black bloc burning American flags, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 305-P)
  - David Dellinger with American Indian Movement leaders Republican convention Chicago, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 306-P)
  - Andrew Hoffman DNC Chicago, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 307-P)
  - Congresswoman Shirly Chisolm DNC Chicago also abortion protest stuff, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 308-P)
  - Charles King with his partner Keith Williams ? Director of Housing Works at public forum on AIDS, American Indian Movement NYC, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 309-P)
  - Ben and Jerrys concert Central Park, American Indian Movement NYC, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 310-P)
  - Dean Johnson and other drag queens at Webster Hall (I love these) Grady Alexis murdered by cops protest, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 311-P)
  - Palenque ruins Mexico in Chiapas wall carvings pyramids camera was broken some are great for historical value others have red line must be cropped, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 312-P)
  - Campaign march for councilman Antonio Pagan, LES Garden rally with puppets great pix, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 313-P)
  - KKK march Pulaski Tenn good historical stuff especially 2 KKK they are women with hoods and confederate flag. Amazing stuff., circa 1990-2000 (Box 17, Folder 315-N)
  - KKK march Pulaski Tenn good historical stuff especially 2 KKK they are women with hoods and confederate flag. Amazing stuff., circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 315-P)
  - KKK national gathering Pulaski Tennessee, circa 1990-2000 (Box 17, Folder 316-N)
  - KKK national gathering Pulaski Tennessee, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 316-P)
  - KKK national gathering Pulaski Tennessee, circa 1990-2000 (Box 17, Folder 317-N)
  - KKK national gathering Pulaski Tennessee, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 317-P)
  - KKK national gathering Pulaski Tennessee KKK yard sale of badges t shirts etc, circa 1990-2000 (Box 17, Folder 318-N)
  - KKK national gathering Pulaski Tennessee KKK yard sale of badges t shirts etc, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 318-P)
  - Palenque ruins Chiapas Mexico, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 319-P)
  - Protest about Sinead Oconner and pope, alternative fashion show NYC, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 320-P)
  - ACT UP political funeral with real body NYC good photos, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 321-P)
  - Antonio Pagan LES councilman with Guardian Angels Curtis Sliwa and with Lisa (now TV reporter Lisa Evers) at Award ceremony Gramercy Park Hotel, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 322-P)
  - Webster Hall night club with Stephan Prophet working as bathroom attendant other nightlife shots, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 324-P)
  - Viola Plummer's group black nationalists at UN march arrests, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 325-P)
  - Sinead O'Conner support protest at St Patricks, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 326-P)
  - Aron Kay DNC Chicago, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 327-P)
  - Playa Azul Mexico me with girlfriend Marisa Peluso, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 328-P)
  - Ruins at Palenque Chiapas Mexico pyramids, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 329-P)
  - ACT UP political funeral with real body NYC good photos, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 330-P)
  - Squatter protest against Rudy Guiliani also gardens protest Gracie Mansion great historical squatter pix, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 331-P)
  - Puerto Rican funeral Most Holy Redeemer church E 3rd st, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 332-P)
  - Timothy Leary acid guru at Collective Unconscious performance space many shots, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 333-P)
  - Bigotry is not discourse wild art show with naked people, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 334-P)
  - Jesse Jackson DNC Chicago also Sex Pistol band member hired by MTV can't remember his name, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 335-P)
  - Film Director Jim Jarmish with Matt Dillon in nightclub classic pix, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 336-P)
  - Ben and Jerry's concert Central Park, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 337-P)
  - Dean Johnson at Webster Hall wild pix, circa 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 338-P)